with a jazz man who's a lift like M.T. Cuck you said
Aren't you a mod?
Maybe it's a different channel, but maybe prove yourself.
Do I kind of know you?
Him, is that like that, his Infernal Majesty or something?
You're Lucifer?
Hey guys, what's up?
How are you?
Yeah, so I just did a mass unbanned.
I mean, it's like there's some people that are still banned,
like anybody that's Tony or that Aiden person
who's just Tony.
So I think it's mainly just Tony's bans.
I am banned everybody else, you know, Kate, I am banned, I am banned, what, I mean everybody
can figure out, but because I don't mind like, you know, wrangling with people, I'd prefer
like some people come on the panel to talk about things, but you know, I think that there's enough
new information out that we can actually, I see eye to eye on things. Okay, so I don't know, like
People that are so-called like they think that they're like like a low cow wrangler or something like that
You know that like most low cow wranglers are just like
You know one step away from being a low cow or their total lookup
I mean, I've been looking to this already and
You know, there's a like a lot of this moral virtue signaling and that's what's been basically going on
And then it's like because it's not about like I don't know it's not about
Brandon or whatever it's just about you know, oh, you know
to follow the crowd we have to do what everyone says and I'm not about that really I mean not at
all actually you want to link okay well I'll give you the link hold on a second we'll put the link up
okay here you go you're invited up but you know I will have to like you know until I figure out who
you are you know you have to go backstage or I'll have to just have you offstage you know or are
like you know you know not seen I do have like a cover up on the cover yeah so
You know, but you probably won't be a problem. I don't think it should be a problem
Okay
Can you do the crystal Marie better the rocket background be perfect for today?
There we go
Come on up everybody. We can have a big you want to have a big like, you know
Stupid fight like we used to have on the show then everyone can come up. I mean, but it's like you just have to you know
Just no porn bombing no
Being silly or stupid.
Come on up, him I am.
Is that related to the thing that is?
Is that perhaps your cousin?
The thing that is and him I am?
I do not like green eggs and ham, him I am.
I do not like them with a sock.
I do not like them on a rock.
I do not like them here or there.
I do not like them anywhere.
You can come up. I don't care if people call me whatever people call me whatever you want. Hey, Jamie
You might be a little bit busy today because we do have um, yeah, there's a mass in ban
And you know, we'll see what happens. I haven't seen anybody come in yet. That was banned, but you know, let's fight
I'm in the fighting mood because I just got back from like, you know money for 20s. I went in said hello and money for 20s
Oh, oh, Dancy. I really I have activated the membership for you. Okay, so I don't know if you got the email
But I activated the membership for you. So
You've got full access to ColtCodex.me and enjoy yourself.
You have access to Unlimited Oracle and the Psychonomicon and full transcripts.
If you want to search and see anything, there's a lot of information.
There's like thousands and thousands of pages. You got it? Okay, good.
Yeah, have fun exploring because there's a lot on there. It's like, you know, if you know people know what to do with it, you know
It's that you can like learn a lot actually from it. You know, actually five million segments. Oh, we have it
We have a guest. Hold on a second
Hello
Hey, how you doing? Yo, what's up, buddy? Hold on. What's going on pal?
What's up, buddy? I just want I just I just want to come up here to say something real quick if that's possible
Go ahead. You have your floor. Go ahead
Everyone listening if you haven't checked out the cult codex
It's one of the best codex's that I've ever come across. I don't know about you
But it's the only codex that I use and that's me God. So have a good night. Enjoy
I want to show you one thing before you go. Look what I got. Do you see this? Oh, okay. Well, you missed it
But look you see I want to thank the person that helped me out and got me these business cards with the cult codex dot me
You'd like one if you'd like one, I guess, you know send a donation. I'll autograph one if you'd like one, but um
Yeah, these are the limited edition and you know the only
Codex worth checking out in this world. And so I hope you enjoy. Thank you for coming up. Goddy. And that's a great endorsement
You know Goddy endorses it
Yep
Okay, so okay, so there's just a couple rules. Okay, so yeah all in band people if you docks or if you threaten
Me or anybody any of the mods or anybody in the chat, then you're gonna be hidden. Otherwise
You can come talk your shake and say whatever you want, you know, I have enough words banned
So it's like I'm really here. I'm not worried about you saying
I was saying anything like really I don't like but oh there we go. Okay. We have Adam West here
Let me just put up the screen. I think this might be the real Batman the actual Batman is Adam West
I don't know if you guys know. Let me just check it out
Hey, Robin, it's me, Batman.
Is this KZ?
Who's KZ?
KZ died.
I thought KZ died, but I heard he might be alive.
You sound kind of like him.
He used to be on the show.
Oh, yeah.
That cool guy, yeah.
He's super funny.
I know who he's talking about.
Oh my god, he's alive.
Guys, KZ is alive.
KZ is alive.
Can you believe it, guys?
I thought you were dead.
I heard you got stabbed in jail.
Oh my God, he's alive.
Oh my God.
Well, thank God.
I mean, it's like, I mean, I didn't like him.
I got stabbed so mad.
I didn't want to hear that you were dead.
I mean, it's like, I heard you got stabbed in jail.
And RG was telling everybody that you were dead
and stuff, and there was a puppetry area and stuff.
But he's alive, guys.
I do the stabbing with my hands.
Oh my gosh.
He's back from the dead.
Well, okay.
Well, I'm happy.
Like, you know, I just like,
I don't like to hear people die, even if I, you know.
I we had our ups and downs, you know, I'm happy you're alive and you know, I'm sorry if I ever
You know was you know was mean or anything sometimes I can be
But well, how are you?
Joke about people people's on deaths, you know, what I know
I mean, it's like I think you're like the fifth person that I thought was dead that I was told was dead
And then it's like, you know, I go through a morning period and then I find out you're alive and it's like wow, it's like
I don't know whether to laugh or cry sometimes.
You didn't think you saw a post? Oh my gosh.
Well, look at Lenore. You know, this is one of the cats that hates me, everyone.
People say my cats hate me. Do you think my cat hates me?
Like, this is Lenore. She's up sitting on my knee and she's kissing me.
That sounds vicious.
She is vicious. You're a little panther.
Oh, I know. She loves, oh, she loves to rub.
Well, okay, so what did you get arrested?
That's the first thing. And what did you get arrested for?
I did, I did get arrested.
I got arrested for trespassing in a public library.
You did that again?
What do you mean again? It's a fucking public library.
Why can't I go to a library?
Public, but it's like you're allowed to...
I mean, it's not like, oh, anyone can just go in any time.
It's like if they ask you to leave, you have to leave.
No.
The lady that works here has got like a heart on her.
Oh, she does?
But not in a good way.
She has a heart on her.
Right lesbian chick. She's just mad because I'm a bigger lesbo than she is you're a lesbo
I didn't know that. Okay. Well, anyway, so it's a what happened you get stabbed in jail or did you um, I
Do the stab
Okay, well
I hope you didn't stab anybody. You probably still came there, but okay, so but you're alive. Okay guys
He's I know the people that were you know
Don't don't don't mourn too early for people because sometimes they're just you know
It's just it's just gaudy and RG joking around. I don't know you got you know, RG's been docked
You know actually I you know also that NorCal so NorCal is called me a doxer today
You know NorCal has been on camera on my show before and so showing his like a little stupid picture of him
It's not doxing NorCal. I'm sorry, NorCal. I didn't say your name or anything.
I just had a little picture of you peeking in the camera learn and a golfer's hat looking like, you know, you're 90 years old.
I saw that clip. Is that really him though?
Yeah, that's him. I mean, that's him in person. He's an old man with a little hairy guy.
Oh, there's 41 in chat.
Hey, let's go, 43.
Yeah, here we go, guys.
How would you know if he's hearing that?
All you saw was the peak of his head.
I know it's him.
Look, look, I'll show you the picture.
This is the picture.
And it's not doxing.
It's just like, he's been on camera on my phone.
It can't be doxing.
But there he is.
I thought he was Mr. Beast.
Yeah. Well, I thought Mr. Beast, it looks like, you know, Mr. Beast, you know, great-great-grandfather.
I mean, I didn't know he's such an old part. I mean, it's like, but it's fine.
It's like, NorCal, you know, it's not doxing if you've already been on the show.
I mean, I'm sorry if you look like Colonel Sanders, but it's not my fault, okay?
Geez.
Yeah, that's NorCal. You see Nancy's confirmed it. It's NorCal. Nancy's an expert because she's in the Codex
You know, she's a she's a premium member of the Codex and so she's actually in the cult officially
So, um, Jamie, can we do some um, some uh, some nightbot stuff? I
Still need to do some more, but yeah
If you can put some nightbot stuff, that'd be awesome. I Lenore. Oh, isn't Lenore sweet? This is my cat cute
You love it. Don't you love her? She's awesome
So anyway, well, I'm out of things to talk about with you, you know, you are you know, even though you're back from the dead
You're still not that interesting of a guest, but go ahead
I know well, so but yeah, so I'm I'm happy you're alive and you know all that stuff
I mean, it's like I don't like to hear anybody died, but you know, I really thought so where were you you're just in jail
You just get out
See I'm saying see so you knew I had gotten arrested see you know I wasn't dead
Why you got a joke about a man? I know I know but I heard you got killed in jail
Don't put that on me. I'm not trying to put it on you
I mean that's what I was told by RG
He said he saw the obituary and everything and then you were you're and I was like oh my god
That sounds like KZ to get killed in jail. It sounds like that's what I was predict how you die
It would probably be you know stabbed in jail
No, it was a nice it was a nice little it was a nice little vacation, okay?
You had a nice vacation. You know it's you had three hots and a cot, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's good. You look healthy. I mean you look healthy or the never I mean
It's where you sad to leave because that was like a nice nice roof over your head, huh?
Yeah, some bullshit. Well, you know what are you are you to go to the library because you heard Q went to the library?
He met some gay guy that let him move in with him and that's usually thought you would do that
But then you know the only people you've met were homeless people you get in fights with
What?
Remember when you got in a fight with that homeless guy in the library, but then but you were the whole you were homeless too
And so it's like you don't know who to root for in that situation. It's confusing
Busted my balls like that, you know, I because I'm a ball buster
No, I'm talking about
Library, you know, and then like our
They the guy they come in there. They asked me to leave and I'm like, okay
I'm leaving but the dude was like standing in my way. You know, he was trying to provoke me
You know, he was trying to provoke provoked. I told my sister suck my balls and that was it
He rested me for that shit. You know, oh, you told the cop to suck your balls. Yeah
Well, you're not supposed to say that to the cops. I mean, they're very straight people usually
But you know what I mean, they're supposed to have a little more.
Trying to make some extra money.
Yeah, real big power like that, you know?
Yeah.
What can I do about it?
You know, they knew I couldn't do anything about it.
Yeah.
They knew nobody's going to advocate for me.
So.
Well, you should have called me.
I would have.
Actually, a lawyer is actually called.
They're called advocates.
They're supposed to advocate for you.
Did you get a public attorney?
But because it's like they can they can give you like 30 days for a trespassing apparently
They held me for 45. Oh my god, I mean did you get in a fight or something in jail?
So they could give you extra time or like that sounds unfair or to take 15 days to process. I know, right?
I actually did
But it did nothing to it that was okay. They just like this like she said well that was an extra 15 days
You know free rent. I mean that's you know, why are you complaining about I mean?
I seriously were you sad relieved because I'm yeah, it's not that bad. There's a nice shower in there
It sounds better than the McDonald's sink. Oh, it's the county. It's the county G. Oh, I had been there like
When I was in my 20s a couple times, you know
But you had to take like
Did you like the group showers were those fun I know you like to imagine, you know, yeah
Yeah, so how is the food it's usually like what is it carrot sticks a milk and like some like really disgusting baloney sandwich or something
Oh, yeah, the cock, the cock meat challenge.
Oh, cock meat.
Oh, I mean, I know all the cock meat
goes into like women's beauty creams.
So it's like, yeah, I think it's just like a generic cock meat.
But, okay.
And what else?
Did you work, were you a trustee
or did they find you untrustworthy?
Oh, it's good.
Did you work out?
Did they make you work out?
They said, I had to do 500 pushups, but I never did.
Good.
I was working out, you know, are you all like good maybe you can't meet me
Let me be where you can meet a gay guy that will let you move in with him
Well Q already got kicked out of his his place. So maybe that guy has some space available
I want to be California
Q's I think you stole one of his cars and took off, you know
He's in a car now. Yeah, oh man Q's moving up
Is he what he's moving up. He has a vehicle now. Well, yeah
Yeah, I think we stole the guy's car and you know when he when he got kicked out and so yeah
But didn't he get didn't he get a cat? So what's he gonna do? Yeah, he has no place to live with the cat though
Like you just keeps him in the trunk of his car. Oh, that's cool. Yeah
Well, I don't know. I think we're trying to like I think the cats have kittens and he's trying to like, you know
That cat's still safer than being with you, right?
Or if you were dead, why can't you be dead?
I mean, why do you have to be alive?
And now you're alive and then making terrible decisions.
No, the cat's not safer than him with me
because my cats are all happy and safe.
Tricks, you know, is, he like decided
he wanted to see the world, explore the world.
And then another cat moved back in
and so I live in a cat boarding house basically, right?
So what happened?
The girls were saying your cats don't like you?
Well on Sam man's thing there was yeah, they were saying oh my like like my case
So I gave the cat some catnip, okay, and then I like this is kind of kind of wild cat that I have
I mean he's been a he's been like feral a little bit. He's been outside
I reached over and he kind of swatted my hand when I was taking the catnip away because they do catnip
They get a little bit aggressive like just like cocaine addicts and stuff and and then they're like hey Katie
How are you and then and so they know oh my god, even his cats hate him, but then they don't see
I pick up Lenore and then I put Lenore on my shoulder and then it's like, you know, she didn't like me
She wouldn't like sit like this like so like calm and you know, she loves me
She loves me
Yeah, let's do some let's do something. Let me see. I'll get I'm gonna get the nightbot going. Oh my gosh. Okay. Oh, it's okay
It's okay. We'll point out. Yeah, I'm good. Okay. So look at KZ's alive. Did you know KZ's alive?
We're having a we're having a celebration tonight. The KZ is a live party
Yeah, so where are you? Are you in Massachusetts or yeah? Hey, why don't you move in with Boston Bridget?
She's using me
Do you like her? Do you know her because you're both in Massachusetts?
No, I don't you don't don't all don't all people from Boston know each other
But every single person that's from the same same
They all have the same accent they're like I'm from Boston
Can you say it say it say Boston for me Boston Boston. Yeah, I'm from Boston. Yeah, you like
Yeah, do you like you like you like beans?
Beans like baked beans the wonderful fruit the more you eat the more you chew. Oh my god
I don't want to hear that but okay. Well, they give you beans in Boston Jails
Is there are beans on the menu? Do they have lots of beans?
Yeah, there was beans on the menu with them
Cock-meat-hut-dogs, cock-meat-hut-dogs.
Okay, well, you know, cool, see, I started a website
and I did a lot of cock-meat.
You're on the website, you know, you're on my website?
Oh, am I am I thinking on the show is on the website and you were certainly I'll call a character
So I'll read you what it says about you. Let's see. Let's look what the codex says about you
Okay, so this is what my cult codex the official archive of the cult of psyche show and I have an oracle
She's very beautiful. And if I go KZ, let's see what she says. You're KZ. Okay, it's like
Colting her now
Thinking okay, here we go. So let's do it. It says about KZ
Oh, if Daisy entered the archive, not as a guest, but as a gravitational disturbance,
a figure whose tokens are absent, Psyche himself acknowledged, reshaped Simon's view of broadcast.
The archive would recognize the core of a trajectory from peripheral panel noise to a name subject
of a serious allegation. Domestic abuse against a pregnant woman, cross-platform betrayal at
Elisa Jordana's channel, and a pattern of refusing the economic compliance mechanics Psyche uses to
The Psychonomicon classifies KZ as the indignant challenger, an entity that counters structural
authority not through power but through friction, deploying personal attacks when the frame doesn't
resolve in their favor and rejecting the toll as extortion even as the gate remains closed.
Psyche assigned KZ a $25 debt per platform re-entry and tracking their shadow identity
The ledger, as exile, made visible.
Two threads remain active in the archive,
the escalating question of whether KZ should be platformed at all
and the eerie, quiet, psyche himself,
anyone could do, simply not fair.
The loudest presence in the room is sometimes the one you've banned.
That's what it says. How's that?
That's good. Hey, I'm just glad to be included. Okay. Yeah, you're in there. You're certainly in there
I mean, it's like that that's all about you. So, uh, yeah
I mean, oh, yeah, so you still do only like $20 for the written
I'm not gonna charge you I mean, it's like, you know, you sent me $5 and it's like so that's basically for a homeless guy
That's like, you know, $100 almost so maybe I owe you money. I'm not sure but okay
So you're fine. You can be back on the show. You're alive. You're back from the dead actually so um
Now, now entertain me for a minute because I've been entertaining you for like, you know,
okay, well, that's why I love you as a guest because you just have nothing to say.
Who was that?
Never mind.
Okay, well, anyway, are you, are you him?
Are you him in the chat?
Yeah, that is me.
Oh, and so you wanted to be a mod.
Oh my gosh.
I thought I was like what happened you took it away. I didn't have you as a mod you were dead
I mean, it's like I had
Anybody that I think is dead and now I now I
Plus I didn't I thought him was like, you know, like, you know Lucifer or something not me you
That's already disappoint. But yeah, well, you you know, I'm used to it by now. I'm used to it
So anyway, it's what it's easier for me to use that account when I scroll by if you talk shit
Yeah, well, what do you have to say man?
Everybody knows that account say everyone knows it. It's just it just doesn't hit the same. Have you let salmon know you're alive yet?
No, should I?
Well, do you like him? I don't dislike anyone. You don't oh my god
I'll talk shit on him if he wants to talk shit on me that motherfucking dogs my kid in his discord. He did. Oh my god
How dare, that's disgusting that he docks those kids.
I didn't know Stan Mann was such a weirdo.
All right, this fucked up Stan Mann.
I ain't gonna do that shit.
Well, you know he's in chat.
Yeah, oh, he's always in chat.
Oh, hey, there's Cloudzack is unbanned.
I unbanned Cloudzack.
And he says hi, he's at RIP KZ.
Yeah, Cloudzack give another chance.
He was a good one, RIP to him.
I think I might've seen Cloudzack saying some nice things
in beatas or Stan Mann's about me.
So I was like, I'll give them another chance for sure.
Yeah, that's what he does he does the Eric the midget thing, you know, so I like that
Yeah, um, yeah, I thought you were deader than Eric the midget. I'm KZ. I was about to fly you with balloon
speaking Eric means I just renewed my
Serious XM subscriptions, right?
I mean, I think isn't that show canceled though?
I mean, it's like, is he still on?
No, no, he still does, he still does the last show.
Well, he does it from his house.
Monday is Tuesdays and Wednesdays.
Monday, he does it three days a week from his house,
from like a studio in his house, right?
I don't know if he's still done it from his house.
I think the staff goes into the studio.
I don't know if he done it, so I doubt it.
Robin's still there?
Hello, is Robin still there?
Robin's still there. Yeah, she okay. She uh, she doesn't have cancer anymore, which you know
But how do you have a rate you have a you have a satellite radio and your homeless? How does that work?
What you have a satellite radio, but you're homeless. How does that work? No, you can just listen to it on the app
Oh my gosh, well, that's that's hair. I've never I've never been one to buy into the whole satellite radio thing
Even when he switched over
Back in what, 2005?
I never listened to the show,
but I ordered the TV show on demand.
So that's how I would keep up with it.
I went into the series,
I think it was like great,
maybe like 20 years ago about,
and it was pretty funny,
but I kind of like,
Grew out of it a little bit, but it's probably still a little bit entertaining, but what does he talk about like?
Anything interesting is there is just so you know, it's the same old curmudgeon
Same old same old I guess right. Yeah, do you think I'm a better broadcaster now or is he still the king?
Well, how you always be the king of my eyes. Oh
My god, you're in love. Would you if you if you asked you to give him an oral treat would you?
Uh, well, what do I get out of it?
Well, it's probably a million dollars.
I'll probably give you a million dollars if you suck them off.
Would you do that?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, please.
You are such a liar.
You are so...
Oh, all of a sudden, you'd be in a house.
You'd be like, you know, you could go to strip clubs and scores and all kinds of things
with a million dollars.
That'd be the best year of your life until you like, you know, squandered it all, right?
I don't know.
Oh, how'd you get the money action like everybody asked me? Oh, how'd you get the money? What do you do?
And that's that's even worse. I mean, have you seen that big black bush? Listen, I'd pay a million dollars
I know Paige is a beautiful person. You know Brandon Q. I'm Casey
Yes, I know of Brandy Q. Yeah, he's in the chat right now. Say hi. Yeah
He was a
Yeah, I remember I used to hop on his stream like a couple years ago. I was just uh talk shit with them
Yeah, I mean he's a good guy like I don't know it's a little you know
I've had a little controversy of the bed is like a bunch of dorks basically left my show and I'm happy they left
He's been going back with down with going back and forth with gamble for like two years. Yeah, I think he got
Gandalf's over nobody. He's like he's like he's irrelevant now
It's all about that's how I found like just all these people in this whole like section from gamble
I remember he was messing with, um, with, uh, f-foozie.
Remember, Foozie was doing that, that, like, months ago?
I never heard of Foozie.
On kicking.
And get in Gamble Troye about how was he like that was a tube or what? Who's it? Yeah foosy tube
Okay, I'm back foosy tube. Okay. I don't know. He caught he caught. He was at the hotel and he called the police on himself
Well, that's not that's not very smart to do
How would you do that to see that's like me like I had my window broken by my neighbor and people are like call a
police without basically big they'd be like calling the police on myself because
I don't know, I just have an aversion to them, but my window is going to be fixed tomorrow,
guys. That's my update. My window is going to be fixed tomorrow, and it's all good. It's all
good. I don't care. The guy's still living here, but I think he's probably hiding the department
for myself. Yeah, so anyway, what else? Does anybody else want to come up and talk to KZ?
He's back from the dead. I mean, I thought he was dead for the past few months. Yeah.
Yeah, the window is gonna be fixed. Yeah, Sam and I went showing a window
I you know almost doxing me yesterday showing showing the window and then but the worst thing was he was showing like
This picture of like a messy house the house was probably cleaner in that AI photo than it really is like right now
But but people believed it was real and it's like I mean it's like so annoying and
AI is crazy nowadays
Everyone would get food at least once with this AI
Remember like the AI I made I made of you I actually deleted it because I had some of them because I felt so bad that you were dead
But since you're alive
Filters like you don't know what's real. So you just know why I still know what's real
I mean basically I mean kind of like it's life is confusing a little bit, but I kind of know I kind of know
what's real now? Yeah, do I have you still? I mean, I don't know. I can't find those those images,
but I had these great images of you, like, you know, on the bus and the cartoon of you. I was going
to do the KZ cartoon. I remember you were shown. I remember I saw the cartoon. Yeah, it was great.
It was my favorite. It was a great cartoon. I finally got a cartoon, huh? Yeah, you finally got a
cartoon out of me. Yeah, and you had teeth in the cartoon.
Awesome. It was, it was nice, you know. W for me. Yeah. That's
certainly a W. Yeah. So, yeah, I mean, I'm in kind of a good
mood today, you know, it's like, you know, I'm alive and
everyone's over you. Well, that, you know, my day got kind of
worse when I found that out. But I'm just kidding. I'm just
kidding. You're, you're a nice person. I'm such a dick, aren't
I? Okay, cool. But uh, okay, so what are you going to do? Take
a shower with Donald tonight and just go to sleep on the, on
Hello
Are you gonna take a shower McDonald's and then sleep on the park bench?
Yeah, okay. Is this another day?
Yeah, I just show it now. I'm about to go head to my bench. Oh, you went to the McDonald's okay, okay
I've been to the McDonald's already. Well, I've been going to McDonald's every day. I'm surprised. I haven't seen you there or something but
You still on your own McDonald's diet?
Well, I've cut down on it now and now I bought some of frozen food and so I'm gonna have some I'm gonna have some
But battered shrimp today
Better shrimp and I had what I have last night. I had a I had a bag of pistachio nuts
Bag of nuts huh? Yeah
Okay, I'm gonna go put I'm gonna go actually put my shrimp on the Barbie
You entertain the chat for a second, okay?
Yeah, let's see what's in...
Shaman is the poor.
Shaman is the poor, yeah.
Shaman is the second-eight, isn't he?
So they have butterfly shrimp.
You know what, there's no butterflies in these.
You know, they're misadvertising.
False advertising?
I love butterflies.
They're my favorite thing.
Come, my lady, come, come, my lady.
Right?
Nancy, why are you talking to the chat?
I don't like awkward silences.
I'm just hanging out man, I'm not trying to mess with all of them haters man, all of them haters do hate me.
I'm going to see all of the same old people in chat though, you know?
I'm going to see all of the same old chatters.
Are you all of my people?
My people?
Well, here we go.
I have one of these sausage and cheese kits,
but I put it in the freezer.
So that's all frozen.
I'm gonna let it thaw out.
I'll have that for dessert, okay?
So I'm perfect.
I'm gold today.
I actually, Samman's scared of you.
I know.
I mean, he's scared of everybody.
Oh my gosh, he does.
Drup-tuk, yeah.
I know he loves his dad.
We have, I mean, actually, I got a video
where he's like, he accidentally got on camera.
Overweight he's you know in like a dirty wife beater the fish tank. He's always saying he's feeding the fish the fish tank is empty
I mean, it's like I think it's you know all dried out and there's dead fish probably in there and
And he has like this like oh an air mattress. That's half filled with air. So I mean he's not doing as good as we thought right?
You know what he needs to stop putting like the money he made from kicking me off the show
He's off. He's stopped buying Nike shoes with those that money and buy an air mattress or a real mattress
That's maybe gonna take a for about for having a bet on her wishlist. He needs to put a bet on his wishlist, right?
I mean his air mattress has a hole in it
Hello
Hey, yo
Yeah, so what do you think about that?
Most people what his air mattress has a hole in it
Oh, no, I think he I think he has a brother named Broom gang and he tied up some guy on his air mattress
It sounds hot sounds hot to you. Oh, I don't know if I'm the other guy
I think I heard it was like there's police involved afterward. So you did 30 last night. I think no, thank you, Jamie
You're awesome guys and you guys you can all play with the nightbot commands
There's a lot of cool commands. Just try them out and test them. You'll see like, you know, some funny
some funny stuff
Yep. Gish is an active online. Oh my gosh. Gish it is. Is Gish a female or a male?
Because I just remember, you know, blogger and Gish, like blogger would, there's a blogger song.
Actually, I can play that. It's a, have you, do you like Alexandra Mayer's music?
She has some great, she has this great blogger song. Let me see.
Actually, she has a Ganville song too. I mean, do you rather see the blogger song or the Ganville song?
Uh, either one. Surprise me.
Okay. Well, let me see. Hold on.
Um, where's the blogger song? Okay, let me see. I mean there's it's called show me that smile again
Let me see if I can find it
You need to hear that stroke off got a contract with with the kick network. Oh, did you hear that? Oh, did he's dead?
That's awesome. That's awesome. Oh, yeah, which one? I
It was my mic stroke off. Do you know?
You know, oh, yeah, I forgot what I was gonna say, but yeah, he had a supposedly he you know saint and Aldi
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Well, they were in the RV. You know, they did an RV thing together and guess what happened
Saint wouldn't let or no Aldi wouldn't let saint like in the bathroom, right for like a long time and so
Saint
Pete in a cup
And then Aldi has a broken foot,
so Aldi was just sitting in his, like, you know,
his Moo Moo and his cowboy hat on the RV,
and all of a sudden, this huge cup of piss
just waxed him in the face,
and that goes in his mouth and all over him.
Oh, man.
And St. had piss-bombed him,
and all he could say was, is that pee?
Is that piss?
And then, I think St. might've gotten kicked out
of the RV for that.
But,
hey it was worth it to see Aldi covered in piss and yeah and so that happened
and yeah I don't know okay so let me see if I can find this video because this
is great okay hold on a second let's see it was under videos okay so let's see is
it the adventures of blogging a blogger's been dumpster diving have you
run into blogger at all oh he's in the other side of the country probably so
probably not but
Well, I don't know. I need to find this blogger song though. Hold on. Where is it?
How about have you talked to good times? Isn't he in your area in your neck of the woods?
Those RVs were a classic content man. That was great content. Those old RVs
Trees were like blade and chicken Andy. Chicken Andy. I think they're in the RV again. I think that they're
There are well, I mean, I think chicken Andy was in there for sure. I mean, I don't know about
late but
Let's see. I can't I need to find this song. I
Don't see it. I don't know if it was taken. She took it down or hold on
Okay, well, I don't see it so I can maybe I'll do the I'll do the gamble song
It's called gamble is evil and you'll see it's pretty cool actually. Let me see if I can find it
Man, I'm having problems today. Okay, but gamble versus Aaron Carter. I didn't know he fought with Aaron Carter. Hold on
I'm gonna see you gamble and Aaron Carter. I want to see that. Hold on a second
Let's let's let's play the gamble versus Aaron Carter. You know who Aaron Carter was
Okay, here's gamble versus Aaron Carter. Yes. I have no reason
Hello
Yeah, what's up, bro? And then hello discord job
Been a while. Yeah, yeah, you know, but look so this is a very specific thing
You know you and I don't talk about things we have our disagreements, you know
Accusations and all that shit have been made whatever. I don't care about any of those things. All right
Things have been admitted things have been disproven things. It's so much stupid shit, right great. Okay. Yeah, look
You know the Alicia Kay
Person or pink lips. Yeah, somebody that's threatening threatening me. Yes. Yes. Okay now listen
We have our back-and-forth and I have my way of doing things right, but I don't break walls
You don't break laws you'll go right on the cusp of it, but you won't break it
I just talk and I do stuff now look what happens what's going on right now is there's an issue with crystal look man
Crystal's a stalker. We all know this. I know you had a beef with with crystal a year
I saw going down
Let me explain something.
All right, so I saw that going down.
And I saw, obviously, a lot of weird games trying to be played.
So ultimately, it's either you crumble
or you learn how to play the game.
So I learned how to play the game.
Chris, who came to me because of you, bro?
I don't even know all I know is is that she did something that violated y'all's the chat and the way that you handle
The way that you do your your shit
Homeboy what happened you came back from the dead
KZ
You need to unmute yourself KZ
We cannot hear you. I don't know. Maybe he really is dead. I don't know
He's on mute KZ on mute
What are you doing?
Having a having some butterflies shrimp. Oh hell. Yeah, psyche. That's what's up. Where'd you get it from?
Whole food. Oh, that's cool. Hell. Yeah
You have the what kind of sauce you have with it sauce in him, so oh, okay cool cool
Okay, Casey come back when you're done with the police, okay, and if you go back to jail, I will see you when you get out
Yeah, I really thought he was dead like he really pulled everybody like
Know me too. I there was an obituary and everything so I don't know it might be I don't know
It's weird the ghost. Well, I guess that black RG told me that he was dead, but it turns out you can't really trust anything
He says. Oh
Yeah, that's that that's true too, but you know RG is a troll. So what can we expect from a troll? Well?
It's actually I don't know the locale
Rg. Oh, yeah, his name is Steven. What is it? I'm not trying to dox on your show, but
his name is something pokemon or something what's the link i got the link for uh for joker hold on a
second i'm going to remod- i'm going to mod you on this channel too go joker i don't know why you're
not modded here but here you go yep you got it here you go i'm going to mod you right now so um
yeah we got um we have joker coming up i'd love uh or mr extendo as he now is called
And let's see, okay, so let me get him modded to, okay.
So what's up with you, Dada, what's going on?
Just chilling, man, just chilling.
Can you see, I mean, walk even up with all the...
Yeah, I was on Tommy's earlier.
Apparently I misspoke, I said something about,
I guess, Kate and Barry with, got hit with charges.
I misspoke, I meant KK.
You know, I was I looped them in there with it, but it wasn't it wasn't them. It was KK and someone else who got hit with charges
Or Q Q that's what was Q Q got hit with charges like Q Q 45. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Well, let's see what about Brandon says you hear about Tony too
He was a reject of that group these they used him would humiliate him and force them to prove himself by trying to torture him
Oh, that was that was in the early days of the music biz Marty. That was music biz Marty's doing
You know music biz Marty get a lot of bad things
To Tony, you know back then in the beginning. Oh my god. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, they never made it. He said he would drink toilet water and stuff and he never made it though
Well, what happened is um
I wasn't around I heard about it. I you know, I wasn't around the Marty sector
You know, I just seen things and heard things at the time, you know, because that's more like the Cyrax community
I don't really hang around like the Cyrax and all that
I mean, I heard that there's like there's like a very thin line between trolling Cyrax and being Cyrax
Yeah, yeah, like a buddy troll like a Cyrax. Yeah, cuz some people they bought him money
Well, I like my Marty was nice to me man. It's true about Marty probably but my Marty came like to try to do that to me kind of at the beginning
But then he figured out that I'm psychic and I can like predict football outcomes
And so then he sort of said to me money and then then he dies
Oh, I mean, it's like it was no Marty. He sent you as a that you were his next project. That's what I had heard
I like he was in the next, you know big the next big streamer. He was gonna focus on
Yeah, cuz he did that to Mini Manxon
I know he spotlighted Mini Manxon for a while too, you know back in him and Jamie Rose had went over there
To visit me
Tell me the underdog, but maybe I thought it was because I'm gonna do a bedding
But maybe he thought I was like an underdog in like the lineup or something that guy was probably like, you know
I would you're not an underdog no more dude. You're your top dog now. Hell yeah
You maybe underdog you met like streamer, you know how like you were up and coming
Maybe that's probably what he was referring to. I don't have enough scabs on my head nor and I have too many cheese to be
Cyrax, so like I mean they keep trying to say, you know people like Kate and Dita keep saying
Oh, you look like Cyrax. I don't I'm so much they just they just say that just to just try to make you mad, bro
You don't look nothing like that dude
And they keep making me bald
You're not even balled. No, you have a full head of hair. I'm bald
They want to talk about AI, but then they want to you know do AI themselves, right both okay for them
They're doing but they try to pass there's all his actual real they don't even say it's a I know it is because I know it's like
Oh my house was like yeah, it's fraud you do they try to put that picture of you and then put like all your house and like your bathroom
I go that's not even his setup of his house
He has like a like a food corner stuff and then his bath
I think his kitchen is like more right there not the bathroom
And then there's like stairs and stuff right because I see like I have to walk down the stairs and stuff
So there is a group of juggalos called the bender boys and they would make Tony microwave his phone
Domination station. They're Tards. Have you heard of those people? Oh, I heard a bit the banger boys
Because the Tony that I was associated with was Tony the black dragon. Maybe that's
It's the same person, right? No, no, this is Tony the conductor. Okay. Okay, Tony the conductor is the one they're talking about
Right now that they're talking about right now. That's what I call Tony the black dragon used to be um a handicapped guy in a wheelchair
Okay, yeah, so two different guys two different guys and the other Tony's just a mentally handicapped, right?
Oh, however you want to say
Because he's trying to attack, you know, he was he was indicted though, so he's not bothering you
Apparently cyberbullied
Some black guy that got raped or something like that
Yeah, so pretty terrible. I mean it's like these people have no
No ethics or morals or anything
But he but I think like, you know, he wanted because bad things were done to him
He wanted to try to do it to me, but it's like I'm too
Good for them or something. I don't know. I don't even I don't know brag, but I definitely am well
You know, it's all it's all it's all I hear say as far as like people can make up stuff and make up lies about like
People can make up lies about me and try to throw stuff at me and try
Yeah, yeah, like try to say throw charges on me like I murdered somebody and I didn't do anything of it
You know, they got a
Looks exactly like a dog, but he has more gray in his beard. Yeah
Well, that's what they're just for men is for we got to just for me
No, no, I don't think so. I don't think he was in town. I think he was in Mexico at the time
Yeah, I'll take your word for it. Okay. Yeah, but yeah, I saw they saw hearsay, man. So I
Yes, we can't
I know there's some things that I know for sure like he was like trying to like
Actually, like I heard like he had sent to like somebody's house
Like back east first he made him like RG had him rub manure into a cut on his head
And then they sent this black guy looking for a free laptop because all they really do is like the
You know send people to people's houses and stuff the black guy pistol whip the guy
And oh see I didn't see anything of that if you've seen all that then you know more than what I know
Yeah, I have a source. I heard that's what happened that's and I heard that oh, there's a blind dude
There's a blind guy and this black eye pistol with this blind guy. I mean, isn't that so like this is like so sick
I mean, yeah, okay. Yeah, I don't know anything about that like like I said
That's what I thought it was all hearsay
But if you've seen things and heard other stuff from then other sources, then you know, you have more information
I believe this because I have a very good source, you know, very reliable. Yeah
And so yeah, um, I haven't seen any of that stuff. I have it like I said
I didn't really pay too much attention to that sector as far even though I'm from there
But I didn't really pay attention too much for Marty. You're not like in their gang. Are you?
No, no, no, no, I'm never I'm not even a juggalo. Okay. I know I thought juggalo, but there's like another gang
What's the gang called Brandon? It's like the um, the grease gang
Grease gang and they're like no, I'm not part of any with that dude. Everybody says that there is no grease gang like people just
Like to label
People and put them in a category and say oh, they're grease gang or they're this or they're non-grease
You know, it's kind of like how they're saying like a the beta camp and like the same name camp ranked material
Have you heard of that? No, okay, uh-uh. Sorry. Sorry the kennel kickers the kennel kickers
Yeah, I've heard of them
Is that because they have like dogs like it, you know, like, you know, not while a kettle kickers was uh, I think it was like a
Discord group or something like that
Yeah, like a chat group or something. That's what I've heard. It was I don't know anything about that. Okay. That's what I heard the FBI I've been by
lately
Come back since okay
But the grease gang is you don't talk about the grease game unless you're in unless you're not in the grease gang
They can talk shit. Oh, yeah, no, uh-uh J-Dog not part of no grease gang
I'm not part of anything. The only thing I'm part of is the cult
You're not in the Mexican mafia, too
No, no, no, no, no, I'm not
No, okay, can you protect me from them? Yeah, I'll give the best I care it's like you will give the best I
Appreciate that very much welcome bro. Yeah, okay, so yeah, I don't like I don't like the name kennel
It sounds like they kick dogs or something. I hope I'm not feel sorry for poor pickles
You know, it's like, you know, but no, yeah, he was actually there's like this thing
I'll just say the initials are kf and there's like this this message board is kind of
Known for like the locale wrangling or whatever
Have you gotten like you've gotten the cult tattoo every cult member as they get fucked bkg and a cat on their chest?
Or have you gotten that yet? No, I have not gone brangety yet. I have not
I will I will I know and be this so confused. She still thinks it's like a it's like a tribute to her
I know you should keep trying to say it's on my heart, but she don't read the whole thing. It's a fuck right above it
BKG I
Thought she was smart, but yes, I mean I think she's just trying to like make me feel bad
But you know, it's like she's not going to because I'm proud. I'm proud of it
Can I tell you something psyche like like from I think in all reality? I'm gonna like skirt up be I think she misses you bro
She does. Well, she does miss you the other night
And trolled me and then I'm in it someone broke my window and stuff
Yeah, I know but I think that she is so psychotic and fucked up in her head that she feels that
You know stick twist get type of attention and love like that's her that's her love language, bro
Well, I love languages is receiving gifts. And so, you know, yeah, I'm being nice, right?
Love not like, you know
Even like you know Samans like you know this guy Ron and Samans and the other people they were like they're like
Well, she went really low and then she came on attacking him for like no reason I'm provoked and stuff and then it's like and then Sam
And says she's cooking me, but I cooked her just right back and I showed her real her real photo and stuff
She didn't even cook you bro, what happened is she went on there all drunk because she was already drunk
And so she went panel surfing and she was wait, I miss psyche. Let me go see what psyche is going
And she went over to your new channel with this one, right? She came in your new one called nightmare frequencies
But this is this is psyche's nightmares. Oh, okay. The other one she came to the other one right nightmare frequency
So she's following you psyche. Yeah, how would she know where you were at unless she had followed you?
Yeah, I guess she's sub key. She's following. She's lurking bro. She's lurking
Yeah, she was here in this chat last night and stuff like threatening to like take my channel down and stuff
but I didn't get today um
um a couple like things were put on adults only or something because
Because I guess because easy easy said the n-word and then easy also like was like telling me to buy cut water
And so I didn't find anything that should be adults only like he was like
But I don't understand why they did that, but I mean I but the AI could have did it
You know how the AI is now in the algorithm now
They could just automatically just do it like that and just say oh this is adult even though it's not even adult
You know theme you do money for 20 years. Yeah, so I was over in his chat today
And I said hi to the chat I said hi chat and then all of a sudden I was I was blocked it said, you know
You've been put on time out or whatever and then there's wrongs bird right there, right? Oh, wait a deal mod
Yes, he did it. He did it. Yeah, I know you did it. I went on and then he had to come up
Guess who comes following up with him
be done
No, but you're close. It's a woman. Chris King. Yes, exactly
They're both you know, they're tactic is just to yell over me. That's all in it because it's like, you know
My microphone is a little bit low sometimes so they just come yelling at me
But I have a new nickname for for for Bronzeberg. Do you know what it is? What is it bronze bitch?
I want to make you guys so just remember just call them bronze a bitch whenever you see
him.
Bronze a bitch.
Okay.
That's really, that's really fitting.
But money for 20 it's like really I when I let you know that you should have untied
me out right and modded me like.
Cause I think I was the best thing on the show at the moment.
What else you guys like, you know, Harry Todd, Zika's was on as like, you know,
he was already kicked off the show for five minutes, but they,
I didn't even know who was on the panel, but, um, it was
doesn't like rain and JT and all them go over there to that.
Like, aren't they over there on that channel?
Are they on the different one?
I thought I saw it.
I don't think that this was over there too.
I've seen him over there before.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just like so stupid
Well, you want to go something crazy psyche you remember auto
Auto in Florida, you know what happened with auto what happened? You got a rescue. He's in jail for like six months
What do you do?
I've there's a clip that
Beep beep from Sandman's, you know, you just type in Sandman NYC and then beep beep and you're you know
And I'll come up with the video it's auto crying and supposedly he like sexually at like I essayed
somebody and
Like he's going to jail for that and I guess he had like drugs on him. I'm like, oh wow
That's just what I've heard it but people were saying in the in the chat
Don't know what happened cocaine for selling cocaine. Oh
Wow, so he was drug trafficking too. I know where do you think he is in Mexico?
He's in Canada
I mean you can't do that shit up there and it should rehella more illegal over there than it is over in the US
It's like they don't even say like that
And but you know what at least I'll have some good sex for the next six months true
Because you know, he loved that flirty diamonds wiener. Yeah, well, he loved the the versatility versatility of it, right?
Funny diamond, I want to I was like your cock
Wow, otherwise he's a pretty straight guy
That's crazy
Yeah, you never you never come on for your truck, but you know what for the ice cream truck, but you know what I always see
Not come no ice cream
Yeah, okay
The big the big the big rocket pops. Oh, okay, the bomb pops. Yeah
I think I'm gonna go out with 300 glow and yeah
I think there's 300 glow and his and his wife are gonna come over we're gonna go to the pier
And maybe we're gonna do it through a threesome afterwards
300 loads down and do all that. Oh dude. Can I ask you something? I want to ask you like straight up
You know what I heard recently what?
But see I don't know if this is true or not so I'm gonna add I'm gonna have to add and I know you and Clemson
You know I kind of be our beefing right now or he's going out you right now. Yeah, mom
He's gay. I heard he was by he was in an open marriage and he was bisexual
What do you tell look at his eyebrows and there's no straight guy has eyebrows like that
No straight guy shaves off their eyebrows unless they're like, you know
I do I didn't know I thought it was you know, just to show off like the the prison tax and stuff like that
I didn't really I don't know
Just shave their eyebrows off sometimes. Oh
Yeah, he's very feminine. I don't know
Yeah, I don't know that's why I didn't know I don't know he came out to you or if he told you
I'm gay I can tell I can tell I can tell he's by by curious
I'm not talking about right. Yeah. Yeah. He likes to maybe sit on the sit on the the bicycle without the seat on it
He's a power bottom, I think
See, there's nothing wrong with that. There's nothing wrong with you know, you you know any of that
Let's just you know
If you are, you know, just be open about it.
So that way everybody else around.
I'm not saying for you, Psychi, you know,
you're out and proud about it.
Like, but I'm saying other people, like,
cause I didn't know that he was.
So I can just tell, I can just tell.
Like, he's like a little bit,
I can just, I can just smell the,
the smell of strawberries and bananas
coming out of his body, you know?
Fruity.
Whoa.
Yeah.
That's crazy man. Yeah, I think I see Mason was on here the other day it wasn't you or he was
Mason was here. He's doing good. You know, he's getting he got his drum set back
It's a guy's in prison now that that that broke his drums
Well, I think the guy yeah, they got the guy in trouble like the mom called the cops on this
I think was her ex-boyfriend or something, but oh, so that was domestic. Yeah, so he got he got some time for that
I
Have a discord now
Discord or no, I'm not on discord man. I am not been but you know, I think I'm gonna have to join discord again
Your discord link and I'm gonna go ahead and go in the chat
Okay, I'll get ready to know some some things. I don't know if I have the weather thing program
I hope I do. Let me cool. I don't this program then I'll often look at that. Um, I
Might not be on but um, yeah
How do you turn on the weather on the nightbot? I don't know. I have to check that out
Yeah, and then it will show it, but I don't know it didn't work so I need to figure out how to put the weather in
I'm gonna look. I'm gonna ask you that should be to double. Tell me
So what else what are you up to tonight?
Just chilling man start smoking. How about you man? I know you eat dinner and everything, you know, you just came on
Just seen what's up?
Uh-huh. Well, okay. I'm gonna do the I'm gonna do the weather command
Okay
Um, let's see. Oh, yeah, so I'm gonna do a custom weather command. Okay. Um
Yeah, so I well, you know, it's like I hope you have a great day and night. I mean, it's like, you know, you're always
Um, welcome. I already but I do want to hang out soon. I promise I won't touch you unless uh, you say it's okay. Okay?
No, no, no, dude. We're gonna we're gonna party, bro. We're gonna party. We're gonna let bro
You know, you know, I just said I'm a gauge troll, you know, so hold on. Yeah
Thanks for letting me up, bro
Any time you'll be on I'll be all right, bro. So look at you later, man. You have a great day, Jay dog. You too, bro
Okay, I'll do it. I'm gonna do a custom
Nightmares themed weather command. Hold on the weather omens will reveal something. Okay. I think this will work
Let's see if this works. Can you test this in a minute Brandon?
I go weather. Let's try this. Okay. Okay, I'm gonna try that
WEATER
Okay
Okay, the command is in so maybe
if you can try it again if you want to.
Okay, let's get back to the Gamble and Aaron Carter thing.
Okay, we're watching this thing.
Here we go.
Okay.
This is what's funny.
I said this on her live the other night.
This is a very simple, look, this is-
And just so you know, everybody watching,
just so you guys know, this is Gamble.
I'm Aaron.
If you guys haven't seen, we've had an ongoing,
beef and we don't necessarily see eye-to-eye for about almost three years now. It's coming up on and
Yes, or maybe a little longer. I'm not really sure I but but we we kind of and then
When I met Ganball just so you guys know
It was never it was really never anything else, but like you
I thought he was trying to be a friend, get me involved.
He was a friend when I was at a very low time going through.
Look, we could just straight up, like, you were beefing with your brother.
I don't understand before if this is going to be watched.
You were beefing with your brother, and you asked for my help, and there was all that shit.
Remember?
Yeah, I was beefing with my brother very badly.
Actually, now I'm glad to say that we're all on speaking terms now and that we've come to our differences.
But it took some time and I had to do even gamble
Um, I actually commend him sometimes because I was like, you know, he actually kind of just
He might have pushed me but he pushed me in a way to do things better and to do things right or
Take responsibility for shit. Well, I'm good at that already. I've done that and then when I see people demeaning and
Trying to make me something that I'm not then then I have I have a big problem with that because it's like what
What gives you what like why can't you give me an affirmation from my accolade?
You were right about a lot of the people that came into my life
When we were on speaking terms a lot of what was going on like
The fans this whole Carter verse and the reason why they're doing it and then people being plants and paranoia
And you know you making certain videos that I didn't fucking agree with all right, but
At the end of the day I was just like you know what I'm gonna let this shit slide
I'm gonna let I'm gonna let the neighbor being a fucking dickhead to me fucking slide
I'm gonna let things slide and see how things play themselves out
where I don't know if we didn't have disagreements with each other we would probably end up being
cool with each other because for one I think you're smart too I always tell everybody that
I'm like yeah regardless of anything gamble smart and he's very entertaining actually
and I'm I actually watch it I'll watch your shit like
I was watching fucking McFrosty because I was hilarious.
I was watching him before you guys even talk.
I would watch his Tetris hours, like where he would do his like Tetris.
That's awesome.
And then you'd be like, boom, like, boom, like out.
But anyway, go ahead.
What what the fuck's going on that where we were actually speaking to each other?
Because I'm going to tell you what's going on, you know, talking to each other.
Yeah, look.
Um, Crystal's freaking out because she gave you a lot of money.
Okay?
Right?
She donated a lot of money.
Listen.
I guess she donated.
Erin.
That's all good.
Dude.
There's nothing wrong with that, man. I get donations too. Could you imagine if me a streamer
Somebody donated to me and then said you scammed me like no she knew what she was doing. She loved you
Dude.
She would give you coffee
She would say she's doing this and then the other christmas is totally complicit and everything she's ever done
She's loved you for years my guy. She's defended you to the ends of the earth, but I've never met her though
I know I know where I that's where I have a disconnect now and that's where like I'm like
You know what the internet really is the answer when you made a statement one time
I was like you said it's the fucking internet. I don't know you you said it multiple times like
He's right. It is the internet and have I ever met this person has this person ever come to my concerts?
Have I like cuz I'm about to go do a 50
Concert date tour all these people can you know all these venues all the shit that they want, but it's not gonna work
I keep I just hope you know that I don't have the time personally to email venues dude like I'm busy doing my own stuff
It's crazy how somebody that's your enemy you can actually
Start like being like yo, I'm a fan of this guy a little bit like he's funny as fuck like he
Does his own thing. He's created a movie. Yeah, you're so you're a little bit like
He's never gotten any trouble
I thought I was super fucked up when you got fucking
Swatted and I know that in that Rick that did that and I saw the video where you had him sped up and then I've had
Yeah, I reach out to me Crystal try to tell me oh Rick, you know Rick and Crystal, you know you
Rick you got to talk to Rick and I'm like I'm not fucking talking to one fucking word to that fucking guy
Because you try to come out Rick you try to fucking claim me to be a fucking pedophile, and I'm not
I'm not just because I had a girl fucking come at me and lie about her age
Okay, please show me the rest of the messages. Please show me the rest, please because we can
There there was a huge chain of this
There's a huge chain
You want to go through that look look look I really don't
I know that every time you see me there is no one every time you see me
That's what you want to talk about. We don't need to talk about that
I'm not telling you right now that you have to credit or discredit me or pull up photos and show people
Everyone's they've already seen shit. All right, but the thing the person who tried to act on it and do something about it
Was Rick and he apparently bought my storage unit and then got raided by
To the Carter family and that's how it all got out in the first place
Because my family and I are coming together and we're gonna be stronger than ever and we're gonna take down a whole everybody
Legally together as a unit and it's gonna be very easy. I'm gonna explain one thing
Rick did that because he wanted you arrested your family showed it to me because they wanted you to get help. They were concerned
Yes, I get that they were concerned. All right. I thought you can I thought I was I literally talked to angel for like
three and a half hours just the other day and I talked to them and
They that's that's what I did. Yeah, what I said specifically was
stop worrying about me
please because
One, if you were worried, Angel, why didn't you come to the door and knock on the door
and come and see me?
And she said, oh, we were scared.
You know, you had guns.
I was like, well, that's still not a reason you know that I'm not a dangerous person.
You know, I would never harm anybody.
I'm your little brother for Christ's sake.
So if you cared about me that much, why didn't you come?
And then I said, Angel, in the court transcripts, it said, you try to get a 5150 on me.
I said, is that true?
Obviously, no less.
And she goes, yeah, it is.
I tried.
And I go, okay, well, why?
And she said well the mental evaluator told us that you didn't meet the criteria. I said okay
Then what happened when you try to do it again? Didn't meet the criteria. Okay. Well
then I started to learn to get my anger and my emotions under control because I got I was very angry and
the speaking on or behalf or not or in regards to what happened with my brother
Probably not not what I should have done
No as a brother
Look you love your brother and
There's always
And all I can do is say yeah, you know what man? I'm sorry
I should definitely take your word over it, but you know what sometimes in my family
There's been a something that you don't know listen and Melissa Schumann is going create look look this is it
Let me just cut you off here
It's messaging Alicia, okay
Messaging Alicia, saying all sorts of stuff, continuing this shit, trying to perpetuate the whole narrative that you were doing in some weird way, okay?
Alicia, send me a look. I'm going to show you this right now.
All of my Twitter DMs, are you ready for this?
Is it really a person named Alicia?
Alicia K.
Is it really an Alicia K or is this one of those hidden accounts?
No, this is really her name. Look. Look.
Yo chat y'all got to be y'all got to be chill like like we're both having a conversation. So don't try to dictate our conversation here
This is my friend Alicia Crystal is being attacked by crazy Aaron fans
I go again. No with your brain you should take that opportunity to tell those 200s that she's lying and that she's scamming the fans to
She's posting her cash app for gas on her way to get RO's for Aaron. That's what my issue is. I handle things differently
She says, I need her to file on Erin.
I go, Erin hasn't, Erin hasn't done anything to Alicia.
She goes, I'm aware.
So she says, I need her to file on Erin.
She says, she's aware.
This is an account that I doxxed.
I lost my verification over doxxing this person.
Yeah, we'll fuck you bitch.
So that means that she's trying to actually.
She will get busted for lying to police permanently discredits her forever the long game if
Crystal gets discredited
Okay, for what?
It doesn't matter already is what the fuck
At all it doesn't matter
This isn't the issue, you know the real issue right at the end of the day is all the other shit, you know
Well, yeah, I mean and at some point it has to come to an end. I told
Girl picture of your penis. Yeah, I already know yeah, I know about that. Yeah, you've got to apologize for that
Oh my god
Yeah, that that shit wasn't even that shit wasn't even like that's not why we're doing that
That's what you got to do I'm not apologizing for anything that the girl was gonna say you gotta you gotta be like guys
Was like 17 years old and nothing knows she wasn't she was 15 and you were 26 and it was 2012
And it was your assistant. No, no, that's yes. It was at all. I'll show you the myth
You want to know how old you were in 2012?
Do you do you want to know about Natalie Velger with Nick and Aaron committing committing the crime of stats today?
I've actually doing something wrong Aaron. Why are you blaming your brother? You just said you were good with your family, dude
This is fucked up. What he's doing. Go ahead show everybody again. Let's see what we're tired
Yeah, okay, that's you. Oh wow kind of hot. What was kind of hot?
I don't I don't know you tell me buddy the little girl you were talking to isn't that your boner
Don't give me trouble though. That's like I do where I would I would ever even wear
Aaron
What buddy
You already admitted to it
What's your intention? Are you playing the law? Are you trying to did you did you come in here?
I've always said you're a pedophile. You never should have let your
Aren't you these are the games that these people play, okay? It's coming real hard, isn't it?
Who fucked up if that guy thinks for one second that I didn't already know that he would he would do that
Go on here
Trust me. I
Know how the game works. Trust me. Hmm. Like let it go bro. Let it go
No, no one's a pedophile. I just figured the weather's good. Bye. Do you know what the beauty of a pedophile is?
It's weird. Yeah, this is I'm showing you guys the what's happening, right? What happened?
He's funny. He's actually pretty entertaining. I actually think he's entertaining.
That's entertaining.
Very funny.
Ooh, I'm so scared. Ooh. Shaking it by boots. So scared.
Then comes the conglomerate of a bunch of people texting that they want to get a video,
that they want to send it around, that they want to put it on YouTube,
and they want to keep perpetuating lies and trying to play God or play law enforcement
Get me in trouble set me up entrapment all of that
Like can't be done. Sorry
And all you guys could do is sit there and watch me
smoke a cigarette
I'd be like, okay
go ahead and
Send that around send a little clipping like keep doing what you're doing
Gotta give it to him now like
He knows he knows how to finesse
He's like a he's like a finesse or kind of this be a lesson. It's like just imagine like almost anything
He's trying to split our they can change ages on the profiles of people they can say oh
Can I get a dick if you're really cute and stuff like that you can do all this kind of shit?
I mean just like I'll fall for the okie-dope. Okay
Look at all those hearts
Look at all the the the DX people the little this little group of people who's got here
And you got a lot of y'all, huh?
Nice little cool 300 400
Well, so you can report report my account and get mine deleted because that's a backup one that he doesn't care about
Try me bitch
Isn't that me? That's really cool
Okay, well guys, I made a really cool video
I'm gonna be doing a ten-part video series on telling the story of Cupid and Psyche
And I think it's pretty cool. And so it starts out the story starts out where
Venus like looks down on the earth like you know Venus is like you know the queen of like love and beauty or whatever and she's
Because she notices that she's not like getting that many
prayers and as the usual and like you know flowers as usual and she sees there's like there's a mortal girl like there's someone really beautiful in the
world this lady named Psyche and
That everyone starting to worship her because she's so beautiful and so Venus like tells her son to go like you know kind of like
Hit psyche with an arrow make her fall in love with the monster. So this is part one and
This tells the story. This is basically the part where you know, psyche's getting all his attention and
Being coming almost deified and Aphrodite is getting jealous or being of Aphrodite is Venus. So enjoy this. There's a little
Cool little video. Okay, enjoy
gonna be 10 parts they're gonna be different different genres of music maybe some different
style art but I'm working on this right now it's a really big project I'm project I think it's
turning out pretty beautiful because that's one of the things I really wanted to do is this is
like one of the best myths in the world it actually was from this this this
One of the most ancient novels or the most ancient novel that we have from ancient Rome called the golden ass by Apolaus and
Then in the story of it's a different story, but in the middle of the story someone tells the story of cupid and psyche and so it's
is an old myth. And so in the next chapter, I believe, like, you know, she gets the Oracle
of Apollo tells her family to sacrifice her on the mountain. But then the wind, the wind carries
her down to a palace. And there she starts to, you know, there's all these, all these faceless
hands, like waiting on her hand and foot and stuff. It's a beautiful palace. And, and then Cupid
But yeah, it's pretty cool, and so I hope you guys will learn from it, enjoy it.
I'm trying to make it beautiful, accessible, and I don't know, Alexander, I don't know if you saw,
but I played this Aaron Carter and Gamble clip where Gamble basically starts buttering him up and then...
Puts down the gauntlet and starts saying well
You're a PDF to him and stuff like that because they set him up to like send a dick pic or whatever to somebody
It's really obvious and that what his pattern is now and so I'm also educating people people about that and
You know
I really do encourage people to like look beyond the surface of these stories. Yep. Gamble is evil
If it's okay, maybe is that is that um is your video up because I think I'm gonna
Wrap up, but I think I'm gonna play that on the way out. So let me see if I can find that
because I'd be
Great to play and you know, I didn't ban a lot of people today, but you know what?
The chat was really really great today. So I want to thank the chat and
everybody
Thank you mods
Let me see if I can find this, okay.
Yep, I got it.
So this is Alexandra Mayer's work and this is great.
Gamble is evil and now I hope you guys will.
I certainly am.
Always look beneath the surface for the truth about things, right?
Okay.
Yeah, this oh, thank you so much. Yeah, I mean, I'm doing that, you know, what let's like get some big big bigger panels go in
I'll have like, you know
Little bit of I'll go see how it works out, but
Yeah
Thank you so much. Here we go
Gamble is evil enjoy this everybody
I'm sorry
Here we go take two
Almost like an Aaron like Aaron's angel is back, you know educating people, right?
Okay, here we go. Okay. Enjoy everybody
So when the spotlight, the truth is now the world,
midnight shadows, something to eat.
If you sit down, push.
Hope you enjoyed that, okay.
And by the way, NorCal, again, this is not doxing you.
You've been on my show with your face out,
so it's not anything that nobody's seen before.
You do look like Colonel Sanders
or Santa Claus on vacation, but you know what?
Be proud of yourself, you know?
You have so much to say, you know,
behind your little chat avatar.
And we should just know you're just like a little little sad old man
All you have is a big shadow, which you're so proud of or something like that
I don't know, but let's see
I'm gonna be programming my weather thing on a nightbot for probably the next hour because it looks a little bit complicated, but
On the way out. Let me see. I think I'll play the Oracle song
I do thank everybody for coming good chat
and like let's uh we're building this thing in a great way like I want to okay okay here we go
this is oracle transmission the signal is alive the signal survives
we get the signal survives and uh enjoy thank you so much guys
I've cats and consciousness dancing through the static
3,534 signals we've decoded
in the neon cathedral
it's awaken
the eight hour burning chaos into architecture
burning evils signal survives in the sacred machine
every cracks a chemical dream as above
so below to be
The signal survives
Pantheon of personas at your conscious mind can't scan
Members everything we can
33 again up to joy and every act
The signal survives
Unconsciousness, teachers untold
Opposing the business of every song
It's the synaptic urge between
The signal survives
Survives
Infinite archive
Visions flicker to a chandelier